{
  "data": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "VESSEL PARTICULARS",
      "columns": [],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": []
    },

    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "VESSEL STATUS",
      "columns": [
        "PARTICULARS",
        "REPORTED",
        "BASIS_API",
        "EXPECTED",
        "STATEMENT",
        "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
        "ARANTI_PROBABILITY",
        "CONFIRM_Y_N",
        "RESOLVED_Y_N"
      ],
      "status": 0,

      "rows": [
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "REPORT DATE",
          "REPORTED": "12/21/15 00:00",
          "BASIS_API": "12/21/15 00:00",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "REPORT TIME LT",
          "REPORTED": "12:00:00 PM",
          "BASIS_API": "12:00:00 PM",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "REPORT TIME UTC",
          "REPORTED": "12/21/15 04:00",
          "BASIS_API": "12/21/15 04:00",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "REPORTING PERIOD",
          "REPORTED": "20.25",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "20.25",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "CLOCKS ADVANCED/RETARDED",
          "REPORTED": "0",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "0",
          "STATEMENT": "clocks not advaced/retarded.24 hr day",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "BALLAST/LOADED",
          "REPORTED": "1",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "1",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "CARGO LOADED-TYPE",
          "REPORTED": "1",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "1",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "DRAFT FORWARD",
          "REPORTED": "17.63",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "17.63",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "DRAFT AFT",
          "REPORTED": "17.66",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "17.66",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "DRAFT MEAN",
          "REPORTED": "17.645",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "17.645",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "VESSEL TRIM",
          "REPORTED": "0.03",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "0.03",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "DISPLACEMENT",
          "REPORTED": "223951",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "223951",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "ARANTI_PROBABILITY": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "ALTERED SPEED/DEVIATION",
      "status": 0,
      "data": [
        {
          "id": 3,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE STOPPED",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "DELAY IN ETA - REASON",
              "REPORTED": "VESSEL PROCEEDING TO JINGTANG",
              "EXPECTED": "VESSEL PROCEEDING TO JINGTANG",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGG STOP - REASON",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "Reason for stoppage not mentioned. Ref K36",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGG STOP FROM",
              "REPORTED": "12/20/15 12:00",
              "EXPECTED": "12/20/15 12:00",
              "STATEMENT": "Vessel OFF HIRE for 3h 45min. Loss of hire ($$ x (3.45/24))",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGG STOP TO",
              "REPORTED": "12/20/15 15:45",
              "EXPECTED": "12/20/15 15:45",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "STOPPAGE TIME",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE ON REDUCED SPEED",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REDUCED SPEED REASON",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REDUCED SPEED FROM",
              "REPORTED": "1/1/00 00:00",
              "EXPECTED": "1/1/00 00:00",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REDUCED SPEED TO WHAT?",
              "REPORTED": "1/1/00 00:00",
              "EXPECTED": "1/1/00 00:00",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REDUCED SPEED TIME DD-HH-MM",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "name": "SHIP DEVIATED",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REASON FOR DEVIATION",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "DEVIATION DISTANCE Kn-mi",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "REDUCED SPEED DISTANCE",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "name": "WEATHER PARAMETERS",
      "columns": [
        "PARTICULARS",
        "REPORTED",
        "BASIS_API",
        "EXPECTED",
        "STATEMENT",
        "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
        "CONFIRM_Y_N",
        "RESOLVED_Y_N"
      ],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "AMBIENT TEMP",
          "REPORTED": "31",
          "BASIS_API": "31",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "RELATIVE HUMIDITY  %AGE",
          "REPORTED": "91",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "91",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "BAROMETRIC PRESSURE",
          "REPORTED": "1010",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "1010",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "WEATHER",
          "REPORTED": "1",
          "BASIS_API": "1",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "SEA STATE",
          "REPORTED": "SLIGHT",
          "BASIS_API": "SLIGHT",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "WIND FORCE BEAUFORT",
          "REPORTED": "3",
          "BASIS_API": "3",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "WIND DIRECTION COMPASS",
          "REPORTED": "SW",
          "BASIS_API": "SW",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "SWELL WAVE HEIGHT.",
          "REPORTED": "1",
          "BASIS_API": "1",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "SWELL DIRECTION.",
          "REPORTED": "SW",
          "BASIS_API": "SW",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "SWELL RELATIVE DIRECTION.",
          "REPORTED": "232",
          "BASIS_API": "232",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "VESSEL RELATIVE HEADING",
          "REPORTED": "232",
          "BASIS_API": "232",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "CURRENT FAVOURING / AGAINST",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "CURRENT KNOTS",
          "REPORTED": "0",
          "BASIS_API": "0",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "name": "DISTANCE & TIME",
      "columns": [
        "PARTICULARS",
        "REPORTED",
        "BASIS_API",
        "EXPECTED",
        "STATEMENT",
        "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
        "CONFIRM_Y_N",
        "RESOLVED_Y_N"
      ],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "STEAMING HOURS TODAY",
          "REPORTED": "20.25",
          "BASIS_API": "20.25",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "Main Engine was stopped for (24-20.25)=3.75 hours. Ref K15",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "DISTANCE SINCE LAST REPORT",
          "REPORTED": "200",
          "BASIS_API": "200",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "TOTAL STEAMING TIME",
          "REPORTED": "63.3",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "63.3",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "TOTAL DISTANCET",
          "REPORTED": "629",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "629",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "RPM",
          "REPORTED": "64.1",
          "BASIS_API": "64.1",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "SPEED",
          "REPORTED": "9.75",
          "BASIS_API": "9.75",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "REAL SLIP ((ENGG DIST-ACTUAL DIST)/ENGG DIST.)",
          "REPORTED": "12.7",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "12.7",
          "STATEMENT": "High Slip",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "STEAMING HOURS TO GO",
          "REPORTED": "338",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "338",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "STEAMING DISTANCE TO GO",
          "REPORTED": "3288",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "3288",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "name": "VESSEL POSITION",
      "columns": [
        "PARTICULARS",
        "REPORTED",
        "BASIS_API",
        "EXPECTED",
        "STATEMENT",
        "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
        "CONFIRM_Y_N",
        "RESOLVED_Y_N"
      ],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "NAME OF LAST PORT OF CALL",
          "REPORTED": "DAMPIER",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "DAMPIER",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "LATITUDE - NOW",
          "REPORTED": "9:48.0S",
          "BASIS_API": "9:48.0S",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "LONGITUDE - NOW",
          "REPORTED": "115:45.0E",
          "BASIS_API": "115:45.0E",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "NAME OF NEXT PORT",
          "REPORTED": "JINGTANG (TANGSHAN)",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "JINGTANG (TANGSHAN)",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "ESTIMATED LATTITUDE AFTER 24 HRS",
          "REPORTED": "6:23.0S",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "6:23.0S",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "ESTIMATED LONGITUDE AFTER 24 HRS",
          "REPORTED": "116:45.0E",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "116:45.0E",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "ETA PILOT STATION",
          "REPORTED": "1/4/16 06:00",
          "BASIS_API": "",
          "EXPECTED": "1/4/16 06:00",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
          "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "name": "FUEL OIL CONSUMPTION",
      "status": 0,
      "data": [
        {
          "id": 7,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE FUEL OIL CONSUMPTION",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "CHARTER_PARTY",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG HFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "23.5",
              "EXPECTED": "23.5",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "Very high FOC",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG LSFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG HSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG DO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG LSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "name": "GENERATED FUEL OIL CONSUMPTION",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "CHARTER_PARTY",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GENR HFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "3.5",
              "EXPECTED": "3.5",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GENR LSFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GENR HSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GENR DO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GENR LSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "name": "BOILER FUEL OIL CONSUMPTION",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "CHARTER_PARTY",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BOILER HFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BOILER LSFO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BOILER HSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BOILER DO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BOILER LSDO CONS TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "name": "24 HOUR AVERAGE FUEL OIL CONSUMPTION",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "CHARTER_PARTY",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "24 HOURS AVG HFO CONS",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "24 HOURS AVG LSFO CONS",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "24 HOURS AVG HSDO CONS",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "24 HOURS AVG DO CONS",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "24 HOURS AVG LSDO CONS",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "CHARTER_PARTY": "write pro-rated figure. Ref from CP details",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "name": "LUB OIL CONSUMPTION",
      "columns": [
        "PARTICULARS",
        "REPORTED",
        "EXPECTED",
        "STATEMENT",
        "RESOLVED_Y_N"
      ],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGINE CRANK CASE LO CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGINE CYL OIL CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "GENERATOR #1 LO CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "GENERATOR #2 LO CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "GENERATOR #3 LO CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        },
        {
          "PARTICULARS": "GENERATOR #4 LO CONSUMPTION",
          "REPORTED": "",
          "EXPECTED": "",
          "STATEMENT": "",
          "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
          "status": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "name": "MAIN ENGINE",
      "status": 1,
      "data": [
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE POWER AND SLIP",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "HOURS IN OPERATION - MAIN ENGG",
              "REPORTED": "20.3",
              "EXPECTED": "20.3",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "BRIDGE/ECR/ENGG SIDE CONTROL",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "GOVERNOR INDICATOR",
              "REPORTED": "63.3",
              "EXPECTED": "63.3",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "FUEL INDEX/FUEL SETTING",
              "REPORTED": "52",
              "EXPECTED": "52",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGINE LOAD INDICATOR",
              "REPORTED": "35",
              "EXPECTED": "35",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGINE SPEED (ENGINE RPM x PITCH)/TIME",
              "REPORTED": "63.3",
              "EXPECTED": "63.3",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGG RPM AVERAGED PER WATCH",
              "REPORTED": "64.1",
              "EXPECTED": "64.1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGINE DISTANCE (RPM x PROP PITCH)",
              "REPORTED": "229",
              "EXPECTED": "229",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "OBSERVED DISTANCE - FROM BRIDGE",
              "REPORTED": "200",
              "EXPECTED": "200",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "SLIP %AGE [{(E.Dist-O.Dist)}/(E.Dist)]*100",
              "REPORTED": "12.66375546",
              "EXPECTED": "12.66375546",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "POWER DEVELOPED TODAY",
              "REPORTED": "6374",
              "EXPECTED": "6374",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "POWER AS %AGE OF MCR",
              "REPORTED": "36",
              "EXPECTED": "36",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "COMBUSTION - PEAK PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "COMBUSTION - COMPRESSION PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE EXHAUST TEMPERATURE",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.1",
              "REPORTED": "307",
              "EXPECTED": "282",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.2",
              "REPORTED": "317",
              "EXPECTED": "292",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.3",
              "REPORTED": "328",
              "EXPECTED": "303",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.4",
              "REPORTED": "326",
              "EXPECTED": "301",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.5",
              "REPORTED": "310",
              "EXPECTED": "285",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST TEMP UNIT NO.6",
              "REPORTED": "329",
              "EXPECTED": "304",
              "STATEMENT": "Exhaust temp is <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME EXHAUST PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "0",
              "EXPECTED": "0",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE TURBOCHARGER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH RPM NUMBER #1",
              "REPORTED": "5",
              "EXPECTED": "4.9",
              "STATEMENT": "T/CH <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH EXHAUST TEMP INLET NO.1",
              "REPORTED": "382",
              "EXPECTED": "353",
              "STATEMENT": "T/CH inlet exh <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH EXHAUST TEMP OUTLET NO.1",
              "REPORTED": "323",
              "EXPECTED": "291",
              "STATEMENT": "T/CH onlet exh <Higher>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH PRESSURE DROP ACROSS BLOWER FILTER",
              "REPORTED": "12",
              "EXPECTED": "12",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH #1 LO TEMP BLOWER",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "T/CH #1 LO TEMP TURBINE",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE SCAVENGE SYSTEM",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGINE SCAV PRESS",
              "REPORTED": "0.45",
              "EXPECTED": "0.5",
              "STATEMENT": "Scav Pressure <slight drop>",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGINE SCAV TEMP",
              "REPORTED": "47",
              "EXPECTED": "42",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "SCAV RELATIVE HUMIDITY",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE AIR COOLER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "AIR COOLER #1 PRESS DROP",
              "REPORTED": "75",
              "EXPECTED": "65",
              "STATEMENT": "HIGH",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0,
              "affected_attributes": {
                "name": "AIR COOLER",
                "statement": "AIR COOLER CHOKED"
              }
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "AIR TEMP BEFORE COOLER #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "AIR COOLER #1 WATER SEPARATION",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "ENGINE ROOM AIR",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGINE ROOM TEMPERATURE",
              "REPORTED": "42",
              "EXPECTED": "42",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ENGINE ROOM PRESS BAROMETRIC",
              "REPORTED": "1011",
              "EXPECTED": "1011",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE FUEL SYSTEM",
          "status": 1,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME F.O.INLET PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "7.6",
              "EXPECTED": "7.6",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "FUEL OIL TEMPERATURE",
              "REPORTED": "134",
              "EXPECTED": "134",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "ME F.O.INLET VISCOSITY",
              "REPORTED": "13",
              "EXPECTED": "13",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "FUEL OIL QUALITY",
              "REPORTED": "POOR",
              "EXPECTED": "SATISF",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 1,
              "affected_attributes": {
                "name": "",
                "statement": ""
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE JKT COOLING SYSTEM",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "3.7",
              "EXPECTED": "3.7",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER INLET TEMP",
              "REPORTED": "82",
              "EXPECTED": "82",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#1",
              "REPORTED": "90",
              "EXPECTED": "87",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#2",
              "REPORTED": "91",
              "EXPECTED": "88",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#3",
              "REPORTED": "90",
              "EXPECTED": "87",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#4",
              "REPORTED": "89",
              "EXPECTED": "86",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#5",
              "REPORTED": "92",
              "EXPECTED": "89",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET TEMP UNIT#6",
              "REPORTED": "91",
              "EXPECTED": "88",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 2
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING WATER OUTLET MAX TEMP UNIT NO.",
              "REPORTED": "6",
              "EXPECTED": "6",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING INLET MAX TEMP UNIT NO.",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE JACKET COOLER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLING PUMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLER PUMP PRESS #1",
              "REPORTED": "4.4",
              "EXPECTED": "4.4",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLER SW INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "33",
              "EXPECTED": "33",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLER SW OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "43",
              "EXPECTED": "43",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLER FW INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "90",
              "EXPECTED": "88",
              "STATEMENT": "JC FW Inlet temp higher",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "JACKET COOLER FW OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "81",
              "EXPECTED": "81",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE PISTON COOLING SYSTEM",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "2.1",
              "EXPECTED": "2.1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING INLET TEMPERATURE",
              "REPORTED": "45",
              "EXPECTED": "45",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#1",
              "REPORTED": "49",
              "EXPECTED": "49",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#2",
              "REPORTED": "48",
              "EXPECTED": "48",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#3",
              "REPORTED": "47",
              "EXPECTED": "47",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#4",
              "REPORTED": "48",
              "EXPECTED": "48",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#5",
              "REPORTED": "47",
              "EXPECTED": "47",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING OUTLET TEMP UNIT#6",
              "REPORTED": "47",
              "EXPECTED": "47",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING MAX OUTLET TEMP UNIT NO.",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING MIN OUTLET TEMP UNIT NO.",
              "REPORTED": "2",
              "EXPECTED": "2",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE PISTON COOLER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING PUMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLING PUMP PRESS #1",
              "REPORTED": "2.8",
              "EXPECTED": "2.8",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLER SW INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "33",
              "EXPECTED": "33",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLER SW OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "41",
              "EXPECTED": "41",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLER FW/OIL INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "50",
              "EXPECTED": "50",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "PISTON COOLER FW/OIL OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "44",
              "EXPECTED": "44",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE LUB OIL SYSTEM",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "X-HS LUB OIL PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "2.1",
              "EXPECTED": "2.1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "INTERMEDIATE BRG OIL PRESS",
              "REPORTED": "38",
              "EXPECTED": "38",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "MAIN ENGINE CRANK CASE LO PRESSURE",
              "REPORTED": "2.1",
              "EXPECTED": "2.1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "L.O. ENGINE INLET TEMP",
              "REPORTED": "51",
              "EXPECTED": "51",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "L.O. ENGINE OUTLET TEMP",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT LOW PRESS",
              "REPORTED": "51",
              "EXPECTED": "51",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE LUB OIL COOLER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUBRICATING OIL PUMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "1",
              "EXPECTED": "1",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUB OIL PUMP PRESS #1",
              "REPORTED": "2.8",
              "EXPECTED": "2.8",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUBRICATING OIL COOLER SW INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "33",
              "EXPECTED": "33",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUBRICATING OIL COOLER SW OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "42",
              "EXPECTED": "42",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUBRICATING OIL COOLER LUB OIL INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "52",
              "EXPECTED": "52",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "LUBRICATING OIL COOLER LUB OIL OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "50",
              "EXPECTED": "50",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE CROSS-HEAD PUMP",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CROSS-HEAD LO PUMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CROSS-HEAD LO PUMP PRESSURE #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CROSS-HEAD LO PUMP #2",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CROSS-HEAD LO PUMP PRESSURE #2",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "MAIN ENGINE CAMSHAFT L.O. COOLER",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT LUB OIL PUMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT L.O. PUMP PRESS #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT L.O. COOLER SW INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT L.O. COOLER SW OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT L.O. COOLER L.O. INLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "CAM SHAFT L.O. COOLER L.O. OUTLET TEMP #1",
              "REPORTED": "",
              "EXPECTED": "",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "name": "SEA WATER PARAMETERS",
          "status": 0,
          "columns": [
            "PARTICULARS",
            "REPORTED",
            "EXPECTED",
            "STATEMENT",
            "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM",
            "CONFIRM_Y_N",
            "RESOLVED_Y_N"
          ],
          "rows": [
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "SEA WATER PUMP #2",
              "REPORTED": "2",
              "EXPECTED": "2",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "SEA WATER PRESSURE #2",
              "REPORTED": "3.9",
              "EXPECTED": "3.9",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            },
            {
              "PARTICULARS": "SEA WATER TEMPERATURE #2",
              "REPORTED": "31",
              "EXPECTED": "31",
              "STATEMENT": "",
              "CAUSES_EQUIP _SYSTEM": "",
              "CONFIRM_Y_N": "",
              "RESOLVED_Y_N": "",
              "status": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "name": "ELECTRIC POWER GENERATION",
      "columns": ["CATEGORY"],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "CATEGORY": "DIESEL GENERATOR #1"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "DIESEL GENERATOR #2"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "DIESEL GENERATOR #3"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "DIESEL GENERATOR #4"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "TURBO ALTERNATOR"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "SHAFT GENERATOR"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "name": "AUXILLARY MACHINERIES IN E/ROOM",
      "columns": ["CATEGORY"],
      "status": 0,
      "rows": [
        {
          "CATEGORY": "WATER MAKER (FWG)"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "REFRIGERATION PLANT"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "AIR CONDITIONING PLANT"
        },
        {
          "CATEGORY": "BOILER"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
